<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hogwarts_App</string>
    <string name="hogwarts">Hogwarts</string>
    <string name="btnBack">Back</string>
    <string name="hat">Sorting Hat</string>
    <string name="gryffindorDescription">
        Gryffindor is one of the four houses at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry in the Harry Potter universe.
        It was founded by Godric Gryffindor, who highly valued bravery, courage, and determination.
        Gryffindor students are known for being daring, bold, and often natural leaders.

        The house primary color is red, and its emblematic animal is the lion.
        Gryffindor crest features a lion rampant on a red and gold background.

        Some of the most famous characters from Gryffindor include Harry Potter, Hermione Granger, Ron Weasley, and Albus Dumbledore.
        The house has its own common room, located in a tower at Hogwarts, and its motto is "Courage and bravery."
    </string>
    <string name="hufflepuffDescription">
        Hufflepuff is one of the four houses at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry in the Harry Potter universe.
        It was founded by Helga Hufflepuff, who valued hard work, patience, loyalty, and fair play.
        Hufflepuff students are known for being kind, just, and always willing to help others.

        The house primary color is yellow, and its emblematic animal is the badger.
        Hufflepuff crest features a badger on a yellow and black background.

        Some of the most famous characters from Hufflepuff include Cedric Diggory and Nymphadora Tonks.
        The house has its own common room, located near the kitchens, and its motto is "Hard work and loyalty."
    </string>
    <string name="ravenclawDescription">
        Ravenclaw is one of the four houses at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry in the Harry Potter universe.
        It was founded by Rowena Ravenclaw, who highly valued intelligence, wisdom, and creativity.
        Ravenclaw students are known for being clever, independent, and often academic achievers.

        The house primary color is blue, and its emblematic animal is the eagle.
        Raven claw crest features an eagle on a blue and silver background.

        Some of the most famous characters from Ravenclaw include Luna Lovegood and Cho Chang.
        The house has its own common room, located at the top of a tower, and its motto is "Wisdom and creativity."
    </string>
    <string name="slytherinDescription">
        Slytherin is one of the four houses at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry in the Harry Potter universe.
        It was founded by Salazar Slytherin, who valued ambition, cunning, resourcefulness, and determination.
        Slytherin students are known for being ambitious, clever, and often driven to succeed at any cost.

        The house primary color is green, and its emblematic animal is the serpent.
        Slytherin crest features a serpent on a green and silver background.

        Some of the most famous characters from Slytherin include Severus Snape, Draco Malfoy, and Tom Riddle (Lord Voldemort).
        The house has its own common room, located in the dungeons, and its motto is "Ambition and cunning."
    </string>
</resources>
